I think we could
have this very unusual
combination of very fast
GDP growth and high
unemployment or at least
underemployment or low
wage jobs a lot
of low wage jobs
high inequality I don't
think that's a macro
correct me if I'm
wrong don't think that's
a macroeconomic combination we've
ever seen before You
think of fast growth
you're like well okay
maybe there's inflation but
you're not gonna have
high unemployment when there's
fast growth I think
this technology is a
different because it's extreme
in the way it's
gonna generate value
but also because it's
moving up the cognitive
waterline there's gonna be
unfortunately a whole class
of people who are
think across a of
going to have a
hard time coping And
that's really a problem
we need to to
get to the you
just asked there's a
few things Anthropic is
doing One is we've
for almost a now
what we call the
Economic Index which is
tracking how our are
in real time